**≥** serhiiraikovskyi33@outlook.com

☆ Jacksonville, United State

+1 774 320 1500

### About me

Prolific, Front end web developer with a passion for metrics and beating former "best-yets.", Well-versed in Front-End development. Recently throughout my 3 years career as a software developer I've focused on developing scalable and well documented code. I enjoy working collaboratively but can also run with projects on my own. Decreased rework by 18% and costs by 12% and consistently receive high user experience scores for all web development projects.

### **Skills**

HTML, CSS, Javascript, JQuery

**Angular** 

React, Next.js, Vue.js

Git, GitHub, GitBucket

Linux (Ubuntu, CentOS)
Administration

AWS, MS Azure devOps, Vagrant

**Docker, Kubernetes** 

### **Education**

Bachelor of Science (BS), Computer science

Saint Johns River State College, United State 2009 - 2013

## Serhii Raikovskyi

# Front-end Developer

### Work experience

### Frontend developer

From November 2016 to September 2017 LEONI

- This company offer web development and graphic design services
- I was responsible for design mockups, content management and React theme customization. Most of the React work was theme configuration and CSS changes.
- Maintained graphic standards and branding throughout the product's interfaces.

### Angular developer

From October 2017 to April 2019 Luxoft

- Worked on Angular.js, Implemented websites, mobile applications, and landing pages from concept through deployment.
- Standardized all output with a new, responsive, mobile-first approach and strategy.
- Assessed UX and UI designs for technical feasibility.
- Developed standard and ad hoc reports in graph format as required.
- Collaborated with product team members to implement new feature developments.

### Full stack Developer

From April 2019 to May 2021 Baker Tilly US

- We primarily used MEAN Stack. 60% of my work was doing front end development, 20% back end development and the remaining 20% was dev-ops/sys admin related tasks. We had a few system admins for a 50 persons + company.
- I was occasionally asked to do things such as migrating test database data between environments, doing jenkins builds/minor build plan tweaks, configuring webpack/or ui/unit testing frameworks.

### Frontend Developer

From September 2021 to January 2023 Livingstone Research

- I was invited as a team leader at this company, Collaborated with 6 web developers, project manager, graphics designer, two QA engineers of the Livingstone company based on daily meeting & discussion, periodically updates via GitHub. Worked as senior development leader in a team.
- Mentored 4 new junior front-end developers on team in expanding JavaScript, React, and Angular skillset.
- Rewrote HTML to meet industry and company standards for SEO and Accessibility.
- Git Manage: Worked on sub-branch, Review code and merge to main branch.